A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Historical Files, SG 1, Series 1 FA389
Rockefeller Archive Center
- University of Virginia (School of Law), January 11, 1949-July 26, 1979 (Box 87, Folder 1474)
- University of Virginia (School of Medicine), February 10, 1968-November 11, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 1475)
- University of Virginia (School of Medicine - Community Medicine, Calvin M. Kunin), January 30, 1969-June 11, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 1476)
- University of Virginia (School of Medicine - Community Medicine, Calvin M. Kunin), January 30, 1969-June 11, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 1477)
- University of Virginia (School of Medicine - Community Medicine, Calvin M. Kunin), January 30, 1969-June 11, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 1478)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Voi-Vu), September 18, 1951-July 24, 1979 (Box 87, Folder 1479)
- Volusia County Health Department, October 21, 1954 (Box 87, Folder 1480)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Waa-Walk), January 7, 1949-October 31, 1980 (Box 87, Folder 1481)
- Walker, Joel H., June 11, 1957-January 13, 1958 (Box 88, Folder 1482)
- Walker, William, September 22, 1954-December 23, 1954 (Box 88, Folder 1483)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Wall-Walr), October 15, 1951-July 1, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 1484)
- University of Wisconsin, February 27, 1951-March 24, 1978 (Box 88, Folder 1485)
- University of Wisconsin, February 27, 1951-March 24, 1978 (Box 88, Folder 1486)
- University of Wisconsin (Medical Center - Robert Coye), November 17, 1967-April 3, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1487)
- University of Wisconsin (Medical Center - Robert Coye), November 17, 1967-April 3, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1488)
- Wise, Harold, December 18, 1968-November 4, 1976 (Box 88, Folder 1489)
- Wistar Institute of Anatomy and Biology (Philadelphia), July 1, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 1490)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Woa-Wol), May 26, 1949-November 17, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 1491)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Wom-Woo), April 4, 1945-December 18, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 1492)
- Women's Law Project (Philadelphia), September 13, 1973-November 1, 1973 (Box 88, Folder 1493)
- Women's Medical College (Glen Leymaster, Philadelphia), January 22, 1969-July 8, 1970 (Box 88, Folder 1494)
- Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars (Washington, D.C.), January 23, 1970-October 7, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 1495)
- Wooster, James, February 20, 1951-April 1, 1962 (Box 88, Folder 1496)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Wor-Woz), September 18, 1951-April 19, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 1497)
- Worcester Polytechnic Institute, April 27, 1972-November 25, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 1498)
- Work in America Institute, Inc. (Scarsdale, New York), May 4, 1978-February 15, 1980 (Box 89, Folder 1499)
- World Federation for Medical Education, March 3, 1972-July 24, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 1500)
- World Health Organization, November 13, 1951-August 27, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 1501)
- World Medical Association, January 1, 1953-September 6, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 1502)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Wr-Wy), April 20, 1951-May 1, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 1503)
- Wright State University, December 18, 1969-April 15, 1976 (Box 89, Folder 1504)
- Wuerhner, J. J., Jr., January 22, 1969-August 6, 1969 (Box 89, Folder 1505)
- University of Wyoming, July 25, 1962 (Box 89, Folder 1506)
- Cross Reference Sheets (X-Yi), April 13, 1945-September 3, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 1507)
- Yale-in-China Association, January 16, 1962-June 27, 1969 (Box 89, Folder 1508)
- Yale University, November 17, 1949-February 21, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 1509)
- Yale University, November 17, 1949-February 21, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 1510)
- Yale University, November 17, 1949-February 21, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 1511)
- Yale University, November 17, 1949-February 21, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 1512)
- Yale University (John McLean Morris), March 12, 1969 (Box 90, Folder 1513)
- Yale University (E. Richard Weinerman), January 15, 1970 (Box 90, Folder 1514)
- Yale University School of Medicine (Institute on Human Values in Medicine - Edmund D. Pellegrino), January 24, 1975-July 1, 1975 (Box 90, Folder 1515)
- Yale University School of Nursing, October 13, 1953-November 3, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 1516)
- Yerkes Laboratory of Primate Biology, October 27, 1953-October 9, 1956 (Box 90, Folder 1517)
- Yerkes Laboratory of Primate Biology, October 27, 1953-October 9, 1956 (Box 90, Folder 1518)
- Yeshiva University, February 2, 1953-April 7, 1960 (Box 90, Folder 1519)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Yo-Yu), December 8, 1947-January 7, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 1520)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Za-Zw), January 18, 1951-April 2, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 1521)
- Zimpel, Max, October 29, 1953-June 30, 1955 (Box 90, Folder 1522)
- Zinberg, Dorothy S., May 6, 1976-May 17, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 1523)